Thank you for playing Inferno!
	I would like to thank Terror’s Martyr and The Good Mister for generously offering to
beta-test this scenario. Without them, this scenario would be an incredibly buggy and unwinnable
piece of programming, comparable to some of the worst pieces ever released by a member of the
BoE Community.
	I would like to acknowledge Alcritas, Andres Gonzales, and The Creator, as I used
programming techniques first developed by them in my scenario, namely:
     •    Alcritas- The Way Out
     •    Andres Gonzales- Fighting Portculli
     •    The Creator- Frame Animation
	All of the custom graphics in this scenario were made or edited by WildKarrdeSmuggler
(myself), except for the Portal on Floor which is by Zaloopa, the Potion Rack which is by Gil-
Glorion, and the Red Rune which is by Draxis. Feel free to use any of my graphics in your
scenario, if you do, please acknowledge me, although you don’t have to.